What you say?
Make fun of amputees? God
damn, dude.
That could be half the show.
ARE THERE ANY AMPUTEES HERE?
WAIT, for real?
Oh, HIM? ALL RIGHT.
WHAT ARE YOU WHAT'S AMPUTATED?
Both legs? What happened to your legs?
Uh I got blown up over in Iraq in 2003.
Holy [\h__\h]
Well, [applause and cheering] thank you
FOR YOUR SERVICE.
>> [applause]
>> BLOWN UP IN IRAQ, ARE WE talking
we talking claymore, we talking cherry
bomb, Roman candle? What was it?
It wasn't a claymore, but it was a
double stack anti-tank claymore.
Sound like a lot of dangerous words in a
row.
I can understand that. And is it Are you
above the knee or below the knee? Uh
below the knee on both. Still got your
kneecaps?
>> Yeah. That's good.
>> [laughter]
>> Not really. I mean, those those go with
age.
You might have been better off. If it's
not too late, I would
>> [laughter]
>> It's too late. It's too late.
WHAT'S YOUR BIGGEST RED FLAG?
Yelling out when I'm talking to
somebody.
I'm [cheering] just kidding. Just
kidding. Just playing with you. I'm just
kidding. Uh two legs overrated,
[laughter] dude.
How old are you? Uh
I turn 40 tomorrow. Wait, for real?
Happy early birthday, man.
What? What [cheering] are you doing for
the birthday? I'm going out deer hunting
tomorrow. Deer hunting tomorrow? Well, I
hope you get to commit cold-blooded
murder tomorrow for your birthday.
There's nothing
You imagine you're a deer and you get
shot by a dude with no legs?
>> [laughter]
>> You on the ground
and then YOU SEE CH-
YOU'RE LIKE, "NO, [\h__\h] WAY."
[laughter]
>> [laughter]
>> The last thing you see is a [\h__\h]
cyborg, dude.
What's that, Colleague?
You should lay out some landmines for
the deer.
>> [laughter]
>> We'll go with the
Edna Mode from The Incredibles.
>> [laughter]
>> All right, Lord Farquaad. What is it?
>> [cheering]
>> This is your son? Son. Okay. Your
oldest. How old are you, dude? 38 last
month.
>> 38 last month. Happy birthday, dude.
Stop telling people it's your birthday.
You're 38.
What you get for your birthday?
You got to go home. Oh, man. You should
have asked for a tooth. Where's your
[\h__\h] tooth, dude?
>> [applause]
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> [laughter]
>> BAD GENES? Don't [\h__\h] blame it on
her. No, no, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
I HOPE YOUR NAME IS MATTHEW.
What is?
Josh?
Damn it.
Hey, listen, man. From one white trash
to another, you cool with me, dog. Don't
even worry about it.
Okay, so there was no accident that lost
the tooth, just no tooth. Okay. That's
Hey, nothing wrong with that. I got more
than all the men in my family. You have
more teeth than all the men in your
family. And that, sir, is a flex. You
hold [laughter] on to that.
You hold that over their [\h__\h] heads,
dude. Good.
But your mother's got a great set of
chompers.
They're expensive. And they were
expensive. So were mine. I have I've got
my top eight are veneers. I got them
when I was 19. And it was like I was
like 26 grand. I was on a payment plan
for 3 years over teeth. My nightmare.
The your nightmare? Yeah.
It looks like you've missed a payment.
Josh, and what was your mom's name?
Donna. Donna, very nice to meet you,
Donna. How about you, gray hoodie?
You got a gun as well. How old are you?
18. Uh, so you've had one for a couple
of years, probably.
What kind of gun is it?
20-gauge shotgun. 20-gauge shotgun,
okay. You have a lot of friends in
school?
>> [laughter]
>> You do? Okay.
Thank god.
>> [laughter]
>> You got good grades?
All right.
What are your pronouns?
>> [laughter]
>> Is that your mom right here?
No.
Your mom, got it. Oh, it's boyfriend.
What the [\h__\h] happening, then?
Wait, what?
You're dating his brother.
Why the [\h__\h] is he here?
>> [laughter]
>> Where's your boyfriend right now?
At work. Where's he work?
Rural King? What the [\h__\h] is that?
A farm store? He's there right now?
It's like 10:00 p.m.
>> [laughter]
>> Daylight savings time, farming's been
done for 5 hours.
So, your boyfriend's brother filled in
the slot instead. Okay. This is weird.
Okay. It's the Midwest.
>> The [\h__\h] it. What's that? It's the
Midwest. It's the Midwest, and you are
the blackest person I've ever seen in my
entire life.
Holy [\h__\h]
That is
Bro!
No, no, NO, NO, NO. NO, TURN THE LIGHT
OFF THE WAY IT WAS, DUDE.
There was just a jacket there for about
6 seconds.
YOUR NAME IS MATT? WHAT?
JUST A COUPLE OF BLACK GUYS WITH THE
SAME NAME.
OH, I love it.
You know what's even crazier? I love
that you have my old teeth. That's
[\h__\h] fantastic.
>> [laughter]
>> Nobody Google it, but that's what they
look like.
>> [laughter]
>> Matt, you're a cool ass guy, man.
Don't stand up. Hold on.
No, just get No, no, no. You're good.
You're fine. You're fine. Watch him.
>> [laughter]
>> What what was it?
Is it a peacock?
Oh, just the design of the jacket?
Watch him. Shoes, too.
The shoes, too?
What the This IS THE
A SUIT JACKET AND SNEAKERS is just the
blackest [\h__\h] that you could really
wear.
I'm dressed to impress, but I could run
fives at any moment.
>> [laughter]
>> At any
You can say the word.
Do it.
>> [laughter]
>> Do it. You're not going to hurt my
feelings.
It might actually boost my ego a little
bit.
How old are you?
50 next week?
Next year. So, 49 is
>> [applause]
>> It's a [\h__\h]
You got a white girl. He sure
He SURE DOES. PLEASE.
>> [laughter]
>> MATT, DO YOU HAVE A
YOU GOT A GUN?
And you don't?
>> [laughter]
>> That's a fair response. He said, "Black
guys in Michigan, guns,
>> [laughter]
>> And I I understand. We end up getting
shot. We end up getting shot. Well,
sorry.
>> [laughter]
>> But with not having a gun, if somebody
broke into your house,
what would you do to defend yourself?
How would you defend yourself?
>> white woman in THE HOUSE,
LEAVE.
>> [laughter]
>> HE SAID, "I WOULD SAY, THERE'S a white
woman in this house, LEAVE!
GET OUT!"
>> [laughter]
>> TINA COMES AROUND THE CORNER STIRRING
HER [\h__\h] tea.
>> [laughter]
>> Tina, yeah, I see right through you.
Just One more. Couple of black women.
>> [laughter]
>> Awesome.
You guys No, Matthew?
>> [laughter]
>> I don't like that they sat black people
with disabled people. I don't know how I
feel about that. Thank you guys for
coming as well. She said, "I'm okay with
that. I love my seat." [laughter]
>> [applause]
>> Is that Rosa Parks who said that?
>> [laughter]
>> Are those titty pillows? Shut the [\h__\h]
up.
What?
Where'd you get that?
You crocheted that? Even weirder.
>> [laughter]
>> Do I want it? Can I for real have it?
[\h__\h] give it to me. Sure.
>> [cheering]
>> No way.
Holy [\h__\h]
What's your name?
McKenzie. Look, they go from Mackenzie
to Donna.
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> THIS IS [\h__\h] AWESOME. WHAT A COOL
CRAFT.
HONESTLY, it's
it's soothing my anxiety.
>> [cheering]
>> We ready.
WE READY.
>> [laughter]
>> OH, THAT'S [\h__\h] AWESOME, DUDE. I I DO
APPRECIATE THAT, MACKENZIE. Thank you
very much.
We're going to your museum. You're going
to my museum. The Warren museum. We're
going there overnight. We're kind of
scared. Well, you should be a little
scared. It's a [\h__\h] haunted house,
for sure. That's kind of the whole
point. I have any advice?
No.
Good luck.
Matt, you got any questions for me, dog?
We love you.
Shh, white lady.
>> [laughter]
>> I I I can't I can't take you seriously
with that
You can't take me serious with the
titties around my neck?
>> [laughter]
>> Now, talk to me like a man. WHAT'S UP?
>> WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE TOWN?
WHAT'S MY FAVORITE TOWN?
>> Have you been? Yeah, yeah, that you said
That I've ever been to?
Oh, man. Um
My friend Jeff used to have this island.
Um
You're [\h__\h] too strong.
>> [laughter]
>> Go sit back there. I don't like this.
It's demasculating. You bodybuild?
Yeah, man. Even the way you said it was
roided out. Yeah.
God damn, dude.
No, I'm just I'm just kidding. I'm just
kidding.
How old are you?
You're 40? Oh, good [\h__\h] bro. Good on
you, man. 40 bodybuilding. You got some
trophies at home?
Couple of Not awesome, man. This is
girlfriend?
Wife. Hello, wife. Nice to meet you.
Are you still competing now?
Year off. Are you going to You're going
to do it again?
No. So, it's not a year off.
>> [laughter]
>> It's retirement.
What was your name?
Zack.
It's not really a strong name.
>> [laughter]
>> You want like a You want like a [\h__\h]
I don't know, Michael or
Duncan.
Or a
Bruce.
Jenner.
>> [laughter]
>> No, no, now that's No, that I Okay,
we're done. That was That's one over the
limit.
That was That was too much. What?
Is a guy in a wheelchair? Are you with
him? Cuz if not, that's so [\h__\h] up.
Did this go There's We got one.
We got a crumple up right over here.
Yeah, your Your name?
Mitchell.
That's a [\h__\h] strong name.
>> [laughter]
>> That's a very strong name.
Need to work your legs a little, but
Mitchell, very nice to meet you, man.
Maybe he doesn't want it.
Mitchell.
Blink twice if you want a photo.
>> [laughter]
>> All right, you little [\h__\h] All right.
>> [cheering]
>> Hold on.
[\h__\h] this guy, whoever it was.
>> [cheering]
>> What's up, man? How are you, brother?
Give me some. Give me some.
Nice to meet you, Mitchell. You like
Mitchell or Mitch?
Mitch. Mitch it is. You got a phone with
you?
You got a broken leg? I think that's the
least of your issues, I think.
Oh.
Do I want to sign it? Sure. Yeah, do we
have a do you have a marker?
You want to do you want to do photo
first? Let's do that. Let's let's knock
that out. Get get over here. Hold on.
Let me ride passenger.
There we go. You got it? Boom. There it
is. Mitchell, how long you been
Oh, there we go. How long how long you
been a fighter pilot?
Just a little Top Gun joke. No big deal.
Don't worry about it.
You got any specific place on here you
want me to sign?
Upper thigh?
>> [laughter]
>> You've been in a wheelchair for 24
years? Holy [\h__\h] dog.
You were only supposed to live till 20?
How old are you now?
32? Let's [\h__\h] go.
Hold on.
All right, love you. Hold on. There we
go.
Is
Is the swastika to the right?
>> [laughter]
>> Well, this Can I sign your knee? No,
it's just fine.
>> [laughter]
>> Only the disabled people. Yeah, you
healthy idiot.
This [\h__\h] walking around all high and
mighty.
You two are together. And what was your
name?
Jen, very nice to meet you. A pleasure.
Is this your mom? You look good, Mom.
She had what though?
You had lung cancer? You beat it? No
[\h__\h] way. Wow.
Would you [\h__\h] give it to this guy?
You had your gallbladder out? So there's
more room.
>> [laughter]
>> All right, for what?
Nothing.
Such a mom.
Cool ass dude, mature at 32. What
can I ask what is oxygen I just imagine?
When you get older, muscles get worse.
You went into a coma in 2016? I can't
fall asleep for a night, you greedy
[\h__\h]
Oh my goodness, way to brag to my face.
They bagged you twice. You died twice?
God is furious right now, dude.
>> [laughter]
>> You just won't die.
That's so crazy. Way to keep kicking
ass, man. I love that you're here.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm one of your favorites, you watch me
on Facebook.
Aw, dude.
Well,
I appreciate you saying it's because I
interact with disabled people, but if
I'm if I'm being honest, I just interact
with [\h__\h] people, dude. Like nobody's
nobody's [\h__\h] different till somebody
treats them different, you know what I
mean?
>> [cheering]
>> Everybody's the [\h__\h] same, dude.
See everybody, you know what I mean?
Some people are a little lazier than
others, but
people are just people. Now, let me ask
you this, in in with you know what
everything you're dealing with and
everything, how the [\h__\h] did you break
your leg?
You seem pretty stationary.
>> [laughter]
>> My mom and dad were leaning me forward
in the the the lounge chair and I
the chair took forward and I fell and
just broke my leg. Mom and dad were
leaning you forward in the recliner in
the lounge chair and you fell forward,
broke the leg.
>> Yeah.
Leave him be.
WHY WERE YOU LEANING HIM FORWARD?
SOMEBODY'S GOT TO MOW THE LAWN.
LET HIM CHILL.
YOU'VE BROKEN eight bones?
>> Yes, I
six legs. Six legs?
I thought you only had the third.
>> [laughter]
>> You got any you got any brothers and
sisters? Yeah, I got two brothers. Two
brothers? What are they doing? Uh one's
a builder. One's a builder. One's
actually going on his honeymoon on
Saturday. One's going on his honeymoon?
>> Yeah, he Did you go to the wedding?
Yeah. Nice. Yeah. Did you walk him down
the aisle?
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, he said ah, funny. [\h__\h] you, dude.
Uh that that tone was never heard that
one before, [\h__\h]
Uh you take the piss out of yourself.
Can I tell you that's what [\h__\h]
comedy's all about, dude? Everybody's so
damn sensitive nowadays. If you can't
laugh at yourself, what are you even
doing? You take it I mean not to
not to take it on too seriously, but no,
but if you take somebody who's like
actually going through a very
not easy life. If they can if you can
[\h__\h] laugh at yourself and take in
what what God is putting you through and
the life that you live and you can take
the piss out of it and find the
happiness and the joy out of it. I wish
everybody could do that, man. [\h__\h]
good on you. I wish more people were
like that. I really do.
>> [applause]
>> Thank you for being an inspiration,
dude. I I I really mean that. I I wish
more people have that mentality. I
really do.
Shut the [\h__\h] up. Okay?
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, she said that she's a wife on a
honeymoon. But yeah, but anybody acting
like that, it's not going to last long.
Yelling out when it's not about them.
You know what I mean?
>> [laughter]
>> He said I'm talking He's talking to me,
NOT YOU.
>> [cheering]
>> UH, WHAT A [\h__\h] COOL GUY, DUDE.
CAN I DO you a favor before I go back
up? Yeah, what do you think?
There's two people in the back row.
That you know, at the top top?
Jillender?
And Bryce. What the [\h__\h] is a Jillender?
>> [laughter]
>> It sounds like something your car runs
on. You got to replace the replace the
Jillender.
Jillender and Bryce. Are those friends
of yours? What do you What do you want
me to You want me to [\h__\h] them? What do
you want me to do?
Just say hello?
Jillender and Bryce.
Hello.
Anyways, Matt, you've been you've been a
[\h__\h] stud. No, very nice to meet you,
man. Yeah, no problem, dude. If I see
this sign cast on [\h__\h] Facebook
Marketplace
>> [laughter]
>> in 6 months, I'm going to be very upset.
That's for you. I appreciate that, Matt.
Favorite comedian for you. You're my
[\h__\h] guy. Come here. Give me one
more. Come on.
Cheers, brother. Take care of yourself,
okay? Mom,
very nice to meet you. Thank you for
bringing him out.
Any Any time. All right. Love you, man.
I'll see you soon, okay?
Gay for real?
Yeah. How old were you when when you
came out? Do you mind me asking? Uh, I
don't mind.
Officially, I was 15. Officially at 15.
That's a pretty gay age.
I mean, I was sucking dick at Did you
say
>> [cheering]
>> Uh, um
People in the back
He said he'd been sucking dick since he
was 13.
>> [cheering]
>> I just want to know how was that island?
Was it cool? [clears throat]
>> [cheering]
>> You know what's [\h__\h] up? There had to
have been somebody who went to Epstein's
Island and didn't know. Like they just
went for the jet skis and they got there
and were like,
"Whoa."
Should have gone Royal Caribbean. This
is very
This is not the Disney cruise I signed
up for.
I wish I was gay. I just don't have it
in me.
I don't think that he's gay as well.
FIGHT.
NO.
AH.
>> [cheering]
>> I CAN'T WAIT FOR THOSE ARTICLES
TOMORROW. Matt Rife encourages [\h__\h]
fighting at his comedy show.
You seemed frustrated. We thought maybe
a gift would help.
I seemed frustrated. A gift maybe help?
Maybe after the show.
>> [laughter]
>> Thank you so much. What is this?
[cheering]
Well, don't clap. It could be a bomb. We
don't know.
We don't know yet.
I came to Iowa and I I guess you
That's because of the
>> [laughter]
>> That's the way That's because of THE
BUILD-A-BEAR JOKE.
>> [cheering]
>> LISTEN, GUYS. I'VE never ended a show
early before, but I
I'm sure you would all understand if I
had to wrap things up, right? There's
Oh, there's one more thing in here.
Cookies?
Are you kidding me?
The blowjob's going to have a hard time
beating this.
It's like the perfect consistency, too.
Oh my god.
Thank you so much. What's your name?
Christina, you are so hot. Thank you so
much.
Oh my god.
You're a grandma?
>> [cheering]
>> Let's put that shower chair to use.
There's already plastic on the
furniture. Let's make a mess, you know?
How old are you?
Say it.
>> [laughter]
>> Say it.
This is dirty talk to me. Come on. Let's
Let's [laughter] start throwing numbers.
40 45?
Are you serious? Are you from Are you
from here?
Really? We got to get you out of here.
We got to get you the [\h__\h] out of here.
Minneapolis, at least.
>> [laughter]
>> Let's just get you out of Let's just get
you down the road. You're not married or
anything?
You bunch of [\h__\h] idiots.
Oh my god. You local morons not marrying
this beautiful woman who makes great
cookies.
>> [laughter]
>> Stupid. I'm so sorry.
What Are you divorced?
How long were you married for?
16 years? God, I'm so sorry.
>> [laughter]
>> How many kids do you have?
Four? Oh, well, that's enough though,
right?
>> [laughter]
>> You get your tubes tied?
You do?
I'm a [\h__\h] Buddhist in the morning.
Now
>> [laughter]
>> These are my sisters. Those are your
sisters? You have three sisters? Uh I'm
the oldest out of nine. Nine?
>> [laughter]
>> What's it like to have such a hot older
sister?
Does she know she's hot? Does she know
that?
>> No, she knows. She does? No. Good.
>> [laughter]
>> Keep her humble. You're nothing,
Christina.
>> [laughter]
>> You're going to be stuck here in Iowa
forever unless
unless
>> [cheering]
>> All right, that's gaslighter.
>> [laughter]
>> What's that?
What was it? What did you want to show?
Was it a bank statement? What was it?
>> [laughter]
>> Your daughter?
>> This is your daughter?
Show us. Are you serious? No, nobody
else can see her actually. This is I
don't want Iowa to know she's out here.
This is your daughter? How old is she?
Is it the 21-year-old?
>> [laughter]
>> This is a very tough decision to make,
you guys. I don't know if you've ever
[laughter] been put in this position,
but
She's in Jacksonville, Florida?
I'll be down there.
>> [laughter]
>> Maybe later on this year. She looks
exactly like you. This is insane. Yes,
she does. She's gorgeous.
All right, so I'm going to date you for
the next 10 years and then we'll we'll
trade up. [laughter]
[\h__\h] this is about to be
the most uncomfortable Thanksgiving I've
ever been to in my life.
Damn. Yeah, cuz if you taste this good,
it's going to be a problem.
>> [laughter]
[cheering]
[applause]
>> What's your biggest fear?
Uh losing my kids. Losing your kids. You
might find them.
>> [laughter]
>> That's bad.
But if one of Jackson's mobile goes
missing, mind your business.
She's in good hands.
>> [laughter]
>> Got your phone?
>> All right, let's swipe out of Instagram.
See what else is in here.
Now let's go through a photo album.
Let's um No, wait.
>> [cheering]
[laughter]
>> Here's the thing. Here's the thing. I
won't open it if you just tell me what's
in there.
I had a lump in my breast. You got a
lump in your breast?
>> a mammogram. You had a mammogram
recently? I'm best friends with my kids.
Mhm. And so I FaceTimed my daughter, the
hot one.
>> Uh-huh.
Yeah, you're not going to ask for ugly
people's advice. Yeah, I totally get it.
So there are screenshots of her and I
FaceTiming. With just a tit out.
[\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> CUZ LIKE YOU KNOW IT'S IN THE PALM OF
YOUR HAND.
DID YOU GET THE RESULTS BACK? YES.
You're okay? I'm okay. Need a second
opinion?
>> [laughter]
>> You sure?
Text messages.
Text Maggie. Is that Maggie, your
daughter?
>> [cheering]
>> FaceTimed her.
Maggie, that is not YOUR ANGLE.
>> [cheering]
>> WHERE ARE YOU RIGHT NOW?
HUNGOVER AS [\h__\h]
>> [cheering and applause]
>> Oh my god.
>> [laughter]
>> Do you Do you Do you know how hot your
mom is?
I know. I know. You're well aware of
your competition, right? Like
You know you can't bring anybody home. I
know. Um your mom was stupid enough to
to give me her phone and I was going
through you guys' text history.
And uh
gross.
>> [laughter]
>> But I'm glad I'm glad she got that lump
checked out though. I checked it out.
Everything's totally okay. Suck in the
[laughter] tummy in.
Everything's totally all right.
>> SEE YOUR TITTIES?
>> [cheering]
[cheering]
[applause]
>> DID YOU UH SURE DID.
Sure did.
And um You're a lucky [\h__\h]
I don't know. All right, Maggie, say bye
to your mom real quick.
I love you, Mom. I love
you.
Bye, Maggie.
>> [cheering]
[applause]
[laughter]
>> They are though. What do you mean? They
[\h__\h] them up. What do you mean they
[\h__\h] them up? They [\h__\h] them
Who [\h__\h] up your titties?
>> [laughter]
>> The doctor?
Do you have fake boobs?
[\h__\h] Um
Prove it.
>> [laughter]
>> What do you They make sounds? Like Like
[laughter] what? Like
Like what
what sound do fake titties make?
Cha-ching?
>> [laughter]
>> Thank you guys for coming on this date
with Christina and I.
>> [laughter]
>> I hope you guys have thoroughly enjoyed
watching me ruin this family.
>> [laughter]
>> What was that?
You're lying.
That did not just happen.
>> [laughter]
>> You
Was that A REAL THING?
>> [cheering]
>> SHE HAS A SQUEAKY toy in her titties.
And you're talking to a doll.
That's crazy. [cheering]
>> [laughter]
>> What?
I don't think that's a mistake. I think
that's the best thing to have ever
happened.
>> [laughter]
>> You can get squeaky toys inside your
titties?
>> [laughter]
>> Can you customize them like a Tesla
horn?
What made you get them done?
Four kids? You breastfeed?
Two of them?
Damn.
Cuz you know what goes great with
cookies?
Milk.
Sell them on.
>> [laughter]
>> Last time I was in Iowa, a woman gave me
cookies on stage.
Her name's Christina.
And I haven't spoken to her in forever.
Is there any chance she's at the show?
Wait, SHUT THE [\h__\h] UP.
>> [cheering]
>> CHRISTINA!
HOW HAVE YOU BEEN?
>> [laughter]
>> YOUR DAUGHTER'S GREAT.
YEAH, WHAT HAPPENED? OKAY, CLEARLY
THERE'S A lot of people here who have no
idea what happened. Um [laughter]
oh yeah, I forgot her titties squeak.
>> [cheering]
>> Do they still squeak?
SHUT THE [\h__\h] UP, DUDE.
WHAT? [screaming]
YOU NEVER CHANGED UP. You are still the
original Christina, and I adore you. One
more time.
WELCOME TO IOWA.
>> [cheering]
[cheering]
>> OH MY GOODNESS.
THAT'S WHAT happens when you get your
titties on a Petsmart.
How's Maggie? Tell her I said You know
what?
Can I call Maggie one more time? For
real?
>> [cheering]
>> Okay.
Tell him you're sorry. You're so hot.
Go on, do it.
Squeeze them.
>> [laughter]
>> Good to see you.
>> [cheering]
>> I made it in the towel.
My bad.
>> [laughter]
>> How are you?
I'm good. How are you?
I'm good. The three of you look
fantastic.
You're a real lucky [\h__\h]
Oh!
Trying to be.
Are you still in Florida?
Yes, I'm in Miami now. You're in Miami
now? Well, we lost a good one.
>> [laughter]
>> Do you have a bath bomb in or is it just
dirty?
Oh, okay. I thought you were just
washing Miami off you.
>> [laughter]
>> All right.
I'm going to get back to the
to talking to your mom. I just wanted to
say hi real quick.
It's literally just her and I and not
3,000 people, so.
>> [cheering]
>> Your only fans subscribers are about to
go way up.
Bye, Maggie.
>> [cheering]
>> Sign, sir.
Check your boobs. Mine tried to kill me.
Do you have breast cancer?
Hey.
>> [screaming]
>> Do I want to feel one?
>> [laughter]
>> Feels like she couldn't have stopped me.
>> [cheering]
>> What is What is your name, beautiful?
You like
Phee?
Nice to meet you, Phee. You had titty
cancer, is that what it was?
Yeah. They end up taking anything off?
Double vasectomy?
Oh, I was like, I'm sorry. Phee?
>> [laughter]
>> Or is it he?
I was right. I was right there. I was
right there. Did you get some some fake
ones?
Oh.
You can choose which ones you want to
bring out? No way.
Interchangeable?
I appreciate you bringing out the big
guns tonight. I appreciate that. Thank
you, babe.
Very sweet.
Um
the cancer wouldn't have caused the the
chair situation, right? Is Is there
Is there another Is there another
condition?
Cerebral palsy. Oh, okay. Okay. Yeah,
cuz you said cancer and I was like,
there's something else.
Something a little Just something Just
something I had an inkling.
>> [laughter]
>> Marlena, how are you, babe?
Nice to see you again.
I met Marlena at uh our Brisbane show 2
years ago. We had a
the clip went pretty viral.
And I called her Stephanie Hawking.
It's kind of like
That was pretty much the clip, but uh
it did pretty well. Wonderful to see you
again. Any chance you're into bondage or
general that KIND OF [\h__\h]
>> [cheering]
[laughter]
>> SHE SAID, "Any chance you're into
bondage or any of that shit?"
Well, we can get some rope or whatever
it takes to get you squirming, whatever
you're doing there.
>> [cheering]
>> Is that what People with disabilities
are sexual beings as well. People with
disabilities are sexual beings as well.
>> [cheering]
>> What was the last part?
Just repeat that last part again.
I'll just read it.
Just read it to me, dog.
Also, you typing it makes me feel like
it's not coming from her.
That'd be [\h__\h] crazy, dude.
If he was like, "People with
disabilities are sexual beings, too."
You know what I mean?
Okay. What did it say?
The only reason I'm asking is because I
think that we would be a really good
mix. You think that would be a we would
be a very good mix.
Okay.
People with disabilities are sexual
beings as well. People with with
disabilities are sexual beings, as well?
I think you're hot. You think I'm hot?
And no one gives a hand job or a
like someone with cerebral palsy.
[laughter]
>> [cheering]
>> I'm about to take you and Fee in the
back and have a little crash derby.
But you're the best part about this is
is like no one is going to prove that
nobody different until you treat them
different. This is always an interesting
moment because I know how
stupid people are on the internet and
they'll be like, "Oh, because I've met
Marlena at a previous show." Some people
I'm sure there's people in here right
now being like, "Oh, if they follow each
other, they must have like they must
have planned that this was going to
happen." I knew she was going to come to
a show. I saw the message. I didn't know
if it was going to be yesterday or
today, but other Mets didn't know if you
were going to be I didn't know if you
were going to be sat up front. I didn't
know if you were going to be over there.
I didn't I didn't know. I knew you were
going to be down here. I knew that
but
didn't
plan anything. Like I did Marlena, did
we did we speak before the show?
She said no.
So,
all the more point proven
that we couldn't really have rehearsed
some [\h__\h]
That's my favorite [\h__\h]
hater comment is like, "Oh, it's a
plant. He planted that person." That's
[\h__\h]
crazy.
Like some people some people have like
very serious conditions that doesn't
even allow us to even have a
conversation to rehearse a script or
let. It just blows my mind. People are
like, "Oh, it's a plant." That's crazy.
Yes, technically a vegetable is a plant.
>> [cheering]
>> Other than that,
there's really no
>> [laughter]
>> no other person.
Amazing. You got to eat your vegetables.
She said you have to eat your
vegetables.
>> [cheering]
[screaming]
>> All right, I love a couch potato.
>> [cheering]
[laughter]
>> About Meals on Wheels, you guys have
that down here?
What's that? She has something to say.
So, you have something to give me?
>> [sighs]
>> I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
All right, what is it? You got a cane,
too? God, is anyone healthy in here?
>> [cheering]
>> Somebody in a wheelchair. Hello,
beautiful.
Nice to meet you. You're okay. Oh, she
got a goddamn laptop. Can we get her out
of here?
You're not even supposed to have your
phone out. What's your name, beautiful?
Marlena.
Marlena? Nice to meet you, Marlena. Oh,
she types it out and then she says it.
Oh, I love I love the teamwork.
What if she's JUST LIKE
AFTER all of this
After all of this
You guys say that word down here a lot,
don't you?
>> [cheering]
>> GOD, DUDE.
I
HATE AMERICA, MAN.
WELL, I LIKE FRIENDS.
>> [laughter]
>> NO, YOUR FRIENDS ARE JUST THAT'S
ACTUALLY
TOTALLY different than what everybody
else is doing.
Love you.
I'm going to be patient.
What's that?
I'm hot?
>> [cheering]
>> Marlena, you wash your hands now.
Just cuz you're in a wheelchair don't
mean I won't beat your brakes off.
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> Well, thank you so much.
Oh my goodness, you are so sweet. Thank
you.
That's all she said the whole time?
What's What's the the the the thing on
on the table in front of her? What are
the squares?
It's a bunch of words. Is this [\h__\h] on
a Ouija board right now?
Let me see this thing.
Oh, man.
Relax, security. You're all right, man.
SHE'S RUSHING THE STAGE.
OH, THAT'S SO COOL. IT'S just a full
keyboard, basically. Simple answers, we
have letters, colors,
oops, thanks, sorry, white power. That's
a weird one.
How old are you guys?
I don't know how old she is. She's 32.
Oh, she doesn't have her phone. My bad.
I took her [\h__\h] board.
The the tray has a a message on the
front. It says, "Hi, I'm Marlena. I use
this board to chat. First, I point to a
square, then I point to a color of the
letter of the word
in the phrase that I want to use." So,
all the letters and all the words are
color coordinated. So, she points to a
square, then points to the color, and
there's like So, there's a blue word in
there, and she'll go to that blue, and
we know that's the word that she's going
to use. Oh, that's [\h__\h] awesome.
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> Yeah, so this looks so much harder than
walking.
Wait, how how how how old is Marlena?
32?
>> [laughter]
>> Can someone see when Stephen Hawking
went to that island?
Marlena,
uh is there is there anything you wanted
to ask me?
I can't say that. My son
has been accidentally killed.
>> So the question was can I get a selfie
after? I promise not to let what? My
cerebral palsy My cerebral palsy hands
touch you. Is that what she said?
>> [cheering]
>> Yeah, we can take a selfie but you have
to hold it.
If you want to come up here I'll I'll
take a picture with you right now. I'll
do that for you.
>> [cheering]
>> I'll do that.
Come on up here.
>> [applause]
>> Oh, big old drop off here.
GOD DAMN.
>> [screaming]
>> ALL RIGHT, get over here. Back it up,
Terry.
>> [laughter]
>> There we go. Get in here, beautiful.
There we go. Thank you, beautiful. It's
nice to meet you. You're so sweet. Go on
back to that seat. HOW THE [\h__\h]
GOD DAMN IT.
IS THIS WHAT WE DO to Mexicans? This is
not okay, dude.
>> [laughter]
>> I got you, sir.
THERE WE GO.
>> [cheering]
>> MY BOY IN A WHEELCHAIR OVER HERE.
What's up, man?
Who you here with?
My cousin. You here with your cousin?
What up? Cousin, what's your name? Jake.
Jake, good to meet you, dog. Jake and
Logan. Logan, sounded like it.
>> [laughter]
>> Shut up. Everybody shut up already. I
can already tell how y'all going to feel
about this and I'm not going to stand
for it. Neither will he.
>> [laughter]
>> Shut up.
He's at a comedy show. He know what he
came for, all right?
That's not true. He can totally be here
against his will. We don't know.
Jake could have just Jake didn't want to
come to the show. He was like, "Oh, the
parking's going to be a disaster."
LOGAN!
>> HEY, HOLD ON A SECOND.
ARE YOU IN A WHEELCHAIR, TOO?
WHAT THE [\h__\h]
THIS NEVER HAPPENED. WHAT WAS YOUR NAME,
LOVE?
BETHANY. Lovely to meet you, Bethany.
And you have you have the Yeah, you you
just manual, as well.
You guys should race.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh my god, nothing would make me
happier. Man, my money is on Logan, to
be honest.
That boy built for speed, not comfort.
Bethany, what is uh You don't want me
asking. What what is your condition?
Just severe arthritis. Logan, this
[\h__\h] dude.
Are you [\h__\h] kidding me?
YOU DIDN'T TURN A LITTLE BIT.
I KNOW, but Logan won the [\h__\h] right?
I didn't even have that much of a
problem with it. He is severely upset
with her.
>> [laughter]
>> You should [\h__\h] him.
That's your boyfriend? What's he going
to do? Beat him up?
Yeah, that's what I thought. Cash in,
Logan.
I got two dogs.
All right, now you your boyfriend going
to [\h__\h] sit in the corner and watch
Logan get an oil change. Right, Logan?
I handle the finances of the school. You
handle the finances of the school? Um
pretty much buying
um supplies for the kids and for the
teachers.
>> Buying supplies for the kids. The one
thing that I have to do that is
>> [laughter]
>> People like your first day of school,
they'd be like, "Bring Kleenex, bring
markers,
bring pencils, bring bring a classroom
if you have one."
>> [laughter]
>> You got to bring [\h__\h] everything.
There was for that?
Now we know. All right.
They still do that?
>> They still do that?
>> [laughter]
>> Where the [\h__\h] is the money going?
Metal detectors?
What when you when you were in school
when you were growing up, what did you
want to do?
>> I wanted to I wanted to get into the Air
Force. Why didn't you do Air Force? I
got this story I got cuz like they got
away from family so they didn't want to
get away from Oh, cuz it would have
taken you away from your family. Oh,
that's so sad.
>> [laughter]
>> Especially cuz someone could take you
from your family without being in the
Air Force.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> What's your What's your dream?
>> Like what kind of like contemporary art
or like fish?
Do you want to sell NFTs or what's your
dream?
>> [laughter]
>> I want to like
make art that hangs up in galleries and
make lots of money. What's stopping you
from doing that? You just got to dive on
in?
>> right after art school when I finished
it was really hard to make your own life
get the criticism and stuff and I went
to hair school and now I'm a hairdresser
and I love it. I'm really good at it but
um
So it's the criticism of people just
being like, "Oh, I don't like your art."
>> Yeah, somebody said it's
a waste of wall space. A waste of wall
space. That [\h__\h] hurts.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, especially cuz it was on the
border, you know?
Yeah, the criticism not it's not fun to
hear people don't like your stuff, huh?
Yeah, you should READ MY TWITTER.
>> [laughter]
>> YOU THINK YOU'RE MORE MEAN TO YOU ABOUT
ART?
TRY MAKING a joke about Baltimore.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> So did the world.
I I to you on that front. It's hard to
deal with the criticism, but if it's
your passion and what if what you feel
like in at the core of your heart you
feel like you're doing the right thing,
the thing you're meant to do, you got to
just say [\h__\h] them. Now, that's a bit of
a tough position for both of us cuz it's
like I
I have to create an art that is not just
for me. Like I have to want people to
want to come and experience it and hang
out with me at the same time, right?
Same for you. You have to create
something somebody would want to spend
money on. Now, lucky for you, there's a
lot of stupid people.
Art is so subjective. You ever been to
like a modern art show? It's just
[\h__\h] this.
>> [laughter]
>> A stick on a white frame for like $4
million. I'll take a white frame.
It's so simple yet so complex.
>> [laughter]
>> Martin. Nope. Who do Who does these
paintings? His name is Diego. Diego?
>> Yeah, he's 23 from Rock Hill, Maryland.
Oh, [\h__\h] 23-year-old did this?
>> Yep.
It's terrifying.
>> [laughter]
>> Can you imagine if you came in here on
acid?
You think you'd walk straight into a
[\h__\h] nightmare?
This is like one of those rugs that used
to be in doctors' offices where the wild
things are, but mixed with that [\h__\h]
Look at the [\h__\h] sun, dude.
>> [laughter]
>> HE LOOKS LIKE JACKSON.
>> [applause]
>> TELL ME I'M NOT JACKSON WITH
>> [laughter]
>> JACKSON.
HEY, JACKSON.
>> [laughter]
>> AND RIGHT HERE. STAND RIGHT HERE.
>> SMILE.
>> [applause]
>> NO, THAT'S ALL. THAT'S I WAS SAYING
THAT'S YOU.
>> [laughter]
>> Remember how the Teletubby sun used to
be a baby's face?
Yeah, that's your Teletubby.
Don't laugh AT ME. DON'T LAUGH AT HIM.
>> [laughter]
>> HEY. IN THE BASEMENT.
DO YOU SELL THE ACTUAL pieces from here?
Like somebody here wanted to buy one of
these pieces, could they do it?
>> Yeah.
He bought one.
You bought one?
Really?
Which That's not here, obviously.
Was it Was it a similar style thing?
Yeah. You didn't just shell out three
grand like that. You art aficionado or
you just like that one piece? I like
that that piece. Just that piece. You
got it. What do you do?
Uh
A little bit of everything. A little bit
of everything?
>> [laughter]
>> He just hands me a receipt for the
painting.
>> [laughter]
>> An entrepreneur, let's say. Feel free to
give me your name.
Are you
>> [laughter]
>> working here, man? I am, yeah.
Well, then you got to say what it is.
Yeah, they work with me. We're We're
best friends. He works at the school, as
well?
WE'RE ALL OH, OH, ALL TOGETHER. SORRY.
What So, you guys work together? Yeah.
We're best friends, and we do work
together. At the school, as well? No,
no, no. In his business.
He's He's my best friend, and he's the
president of my company.
And
>> [laughter]
>> He's the president [laughter] of your
company? Yeah, yeah. And then he he he
had a full-time job at the school, but
he he started working with us. He's our
PR AP guy. What What is this other
business? So, I own a franchises. We
It's like a home It's like service
cleaning maintenance type of business.
Oh, okay. And you run that [\h__\h]
Yeah, we have here in Virginia,
Maryland, DC, and Austin, Texas, and San
Antonio. Oh, [\h__\h] yeah, man. So, if we
threw a party here, could we hire the
services to come clean this place?
>> No, it's not that kind of service. Ah,
[\h__\h] FOR REAL? OKAY, you start with the
walls, man.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, we we we do that.
>> Oh, waste management. Yeah, we pick
waste. We pick waste.
You pick up
Yeah.
It works the same way.
>> [laughter]
>> We clean UP DOG [\h__\h]
>> I FEEL LIKE I'M SAYING THAT I'M A
ENTREPRENEUR. AND AS YOU SHOULD.
ENTREPRENEUR, ENTREPRENEUR. THAT'S YOUR
I'M JUST TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHERE THE
PET CLEANUP WOULD BE. IS THIS like doggy
daycare?
>> Backyard. Backyard. Backyard. People are
I would imagine the case
>> Someone to pick up the dog [\h__\h]
Backyard. Yeah, they got a demographic
for like upper middle class and above.
Yeah, I pictured it was just rich snobby
people.
Poor people are like, I NEED THE WARM.
>> [laughter]
>> HAVE HAVE YOU CLEANED ENOUGH dog [\h__\h] to
now know like what kind of dog did it?
>> [laughter]
>> Not yet. Not yet. I was secure enough to
be able to tell you, okay, this is
Chihuahua.
You tell it's high.
I don't like the fact that you guys are
judging by the size now. What if you're
a big dog and you take a little [\h__\h]
People will think I'm not for real.
>> [laughter]
>> Like fellas, you know how like you ever
have to piss next to somebody and you
want to make sure it's a it's a deep
stream so
they think your dick is closer to the
water than it really is?
Guys, did y'all know that we did that?
>> [laughter]
>> Oh yeah. Oh, if anybody is even in the
public restroom with you, you're like,
okay, I got to get center. I got to get
as low as possible.
>> [laughter]
>> They got to They need to feel like my
dick is UNDER THE WATER.
SO, I'M CURIOUS if anybody else in here
has ever had a scary dream that has just
[\h__\h] stuck with them. Like two of
these that I was saying.
>> Yeah. Well, okay. It stuck with me for
like 15 years. What happened? I mean, it
it would be long to explain the whole
thing, but the end of it was I thought
there was murder in my house and I
distinctly remember standing outside of
my house looking in with the cops and
the cops came in and slept on the floor
of my bedroom cuz I thought the murderer
was still in the house.
And I woke up feeling someone's hand on
my arm.
And it was like long fingers and cuz I
would like went like this and I mean, I
picked I never forgot it ever.
I know you said long story, let's get to
the end. I'll tell YOU WHAT HAPPENED.
>> [laughter]
>> YOU'RE OUTSIDE WITH THE COPS AND YOU'RE
LIKE, "HE'S in there for sure." And the
cops are like, "We'll sleep on your
floor
to make sure you're good."
>> [laughter]
>> Wait, you woke up and the cops were
dead?
OH, [\h__\h] THEY WERE ALL DEAD ON THE
FLOOR AND THE murderer was like in my
bed and its hand like grabbed and that's
when I woke back up. Oh, I thought you
meant the cops were like, "No, we'll get
sleeping bags and like just make sure
you're good."
>> They they did allegedly fall asleep in
bags.
And allegedly [laughter] in the murder
was pressing some kind of long gangly
fingers on your arm.
That is [\h__\h] creepy. The long hands
always creep me out. Whenever they get
like a demon or something like that in
movies, something about long fingers
always freak me the [\h__\h] out. You do
still live in this house? Uh no, I'm in
law school, so it's You're a lawyer?
Yeah. Good for you. Allegedly is
probably why. Allegedly, yeah, now
I have to [laughter] pull a boss.
What?
>> [laughter]
>> She just went, "Why did I
>> Pull a boss is when you just you you
talk and no one else can interrupt you
while you're talking, right? That's what
I just did. Yeah, you did it though.
>> [laughter]
>> PULL A BOSS.
ORDER!
>> [laughter]
>> IT'S SO POWERFUL. IT'S MORE LEGAL. OKAY.
OKAY, SO this is 15 years ago you were
in law school. No, it wasn't 15. I'm
probably 10. Oh, you were 10. Okay. I
wasn't 10. It was 10 years years ago. I
thought you said 15 years ago.
>> No, I don't
>> [clears throat]
[laughter]
>> Objection, hearsay.
I went to Old Miss. It was like brand
new. You went to Old Miss?
>> Yes, I went there. Oh, man. They let
lawyers go to Old Miss?
How long were the fingers? If you're
looking at a normal hand, were they like
another 2 in longer than like like was
it like was it bordering the line of
like it was almost a really good dream?
>> [laughter]
>> I've never even been arrested, so Never
been arrested?
>> Well, almost. Okay.
Keep listening. I was like 19, drinking
tequila out of a frat house. It was You
went to a frat party? I was 19,
drinking. Shame.
You went to a sorority? Yeah.
Which one?
Well, that Arkansas was a state. Cuz I
went to school with a lot of girls from
like Dallas, like Dallas area, that all
kind of thought they were hot [\h__\h] and
Oh, yeah. Dallas girls do think they're
hot [\h__\h] but they won't move to LA.
No, you're [\h__\h] lame. Lone [laughter]
Star is one star.
Yeah, you hot in Dallas. Don't bring
Don't bring that [\h__\h] over here.
>> [laughter]
>> And you want to have kids, do you?
Absolutely not. 25?
Yeah, sure. No?
32 32? Good for you. Congratulations. Do
you want kids someday? Uh, maybe. Maybe
what? I've got dogs and 32, OKAY. TAKE
THAT.
I'M SORRY BUT
DID YOU START A GOFUNDME FOR
>> [laughter]
>> FOR YOU TO have a baby? I'm egg
freezing. Open egg freezing. Got got
you. I like what you're saying. GoFundMe
for you to get pregnant. I was like you
need a GoFundMe.
>> [laughter]
>> People can make donations.
That is not a bad [laughter] idea. What
are you [\h__\h] thinking?
Think of it as a Shark Tank in need.
Like for people [laughter] who just
can't get pregnant with their partner
cuz they need their sperm or their
partner's like they need more sperm or
something. You just bring in a bunch of
people, get it on video.
>> [laughter]
>> Doesn't it you that it freezes your
eggs? Yeah, cuz like where the [\h__\h] do
they What if you don't eat them? I just
I just never
>> [laughter]
>> I've never eaten a frozen Hot Pocket
that the center wasn't still frozen hot.
>> [laughter]
>> And that's probably what would happen to
my
baby.
Like maybe he like he looks dope, but
inside he's just like "Dude."
>> [laughter]
>> [\h__\h] this [\h__\h] is frozen.
>> MY BABY'S REALLY HOME.
>> [laughter]
>> DENISE, LOVE THE NAME, TOO. WHAT'S UP?
What's up with your legs?
Spinal cord injury. What did you do? I I
wrote Black guys. Black Black guys did
this to you? Oh, black ice. Oh my god.
Oh, I thought she said
I thought she said black guys. I said,
"Yeah, they will reach your spinal cord.
They will."
Cool.
Black ice. Okay.
Who's that with you?
My son. It's your son. Do you have a
gun? What kind?
A lot. A lot? What's the What's the
tattoo across your chest there between
your shirt? What is that? It says
peaceful. It says peaceful?
Does it?
>> [cheering]
>> In English?
Oh, in Arabic. Okay, I'm starting to
think maybe you shouldn't have all these
guns.
>> [laughter]
>> Denise,
are you single right now? Yeah. You are?
Okay.
Are you on any of the websites?
Autotrader? Anything like that?
That chair is expensive.
>> [laughter]
>> You got the [\h__\h] You got the
automatic.
$41,000
for that chair.
Are you serious? Somebody's going to
steal those [\h__\h] hubcaps.
That is Oh my god. That should not
It should be free.
That [cheering] seems
$41 is a lot of [\h__\h] money.
What's your type, Denise? What do you
like?
Can't be too tall.
You're into me?
>> [cheering]
>> What are your pronouns, hon?
I'm about to take your mom to the
garage.
>> [laughter]
>> The Oh, are you actually racing yourself
right now? No [\h__\h] way.
SHE'S GOT LIFTS.
>> [cheering]
>> WHOEVER'S BACKSTAGE, play Creed.
CAN YOU TAKE ME
HIGHER?
>> [cheering]
>> OH MY GOD.
If that's it, you can go through the
drive-thru.
You stay up. The [\h__\h] the people behind
you. What do you get? Yeah. What are you
going to do?
I got a hundred for that shirt for her.
She what? She wants that shirt. I got a
hundred for it. Your Oh, your girl wants
my shirt for a hundred dollars?
This one?
>> [cheering]
>> I'll take it. Come here.
>> Hold on.
Hold on.
>> [cheering]
>> How you doing? Thanks, brother. This
money feels fake, by the way.
>> [cheering]
>> Thanks for letting me use your stuff,
dude.
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> Ah, [\h__\h]
Is the plan to go all the way around?
Oh, god damn it.
And there's stairs right here. Get out
of it.
Okay, we did it. There we go.
>> [cheering]
[screaming]
>> I hope she makes you wear it when you
[\h__\h] her later.
>> [cheering]
>> Please don't go spend it on some fancy
chair, okay?
>> [cheering]
>> Put it towards some oil change or
something, whatever you got to do.
Such a sweetheart. How old are the kids?
18. They're transgender. They're trans?
You have a trans child?
[\h__\h]
Now, boy or girl? Girl. Now a girl.
Nice. Can I ask Can I ask her name? Amy.
Amy.
Can I ask the dead name? Dylan. Dylan.
Amy's better. Yeah.
That's on you.
That's on you a little bit.
Where are you from?
Wales. Wales.
Just be thankful she's not a sheep now.
>> [cheering]
>> No, I'm sure she's stunning. I'm sure
she's a bad [\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> Bro, I can't believe y'all just talk
about another country like that. Like I
I would start a war.
Has she been to a comedy show before?
Uh no. No? Do you think she would enjoy
this one?
No.
>> [laughter]
>> This is the great thing about comedy.
It's not the internet. You come, you
kind of know what you're [\h__\h]
getting. It's just a joke. Nobody should
be taking [\h__\h] too seriously. Start to
loosen up a little bit.
Or maybe that's the doctor's job. I
don't know.
>> [laughter]
>> That was the line?
We're like eight jokes deep.
>> [laughter]
>> Stupid.
Unbelievable.
Ask what?
>> [laughter]
>> I was explaining the pressure.
You were explaining Oh, first of all, am
I getting heckled by a [\h__\h] in a
WHEELCHAIR RIGHT NOW?
ALL RIGHT.
Uh it ain't going to be no walk in the
park.
What's your name? Amy. Amy.
You didn't say she was a transformer.
>> [applause]
[cheering]
>> Amy, how long have you
been a woman?
I'm kidding. How long
How long How long have you been you been
in the chair? Uh
2021. 2021? [\h__\h] COVID?
What is it? Hypermobility.
Hypermobility? Yeah, so it over
It feels like the opposite.
Hyper is like extensive mobility,
wouldn't it be?
It's like Rice Krispies, so when I stop
crackling pop Your body's like Rice
Krispies, you snap,
>> [laughter]
>> crackle, and pop.
I thought it was more like Cheerios.
Oh, that's the line?
You guys are weird, man.
Who you here with, Amy?
Husband?
You're swingers?
>> [cheering]
>> Have I ever had a threesome? No, but
I've had a two and a half-some.
>> [laughter]
>> I can't believe you like to swing. It's
mostly in the legs.
No way.
You You got two kids? NICE.
COOL.
THAT'S MORE INFORMATION THAN I asked
for.
How old are the kids? Nine and 11. Nine
and 11.
>> [laughter]
>> Are they twins?
>> [applause]
>> I know technically that doesn't make
sense, but it's, you know, you're
[\h__\h] We're making it work. We're
taking it and running with it, right?
>> [laughter]
>> Have you ever been to a sex club? Have I
ever been to a sex club? No. Never been
Never been invited.
You guys go to one?
Really?
They have ramps and [\h__\h]
I'm just curious.
It
It's an exclusive club. You know what I
mean? I I didn't know how inclusive they
would be. This is good. This is
wonderful. That's [\h__\h] [laughter]
awesome.
What's the uh initiation fee?
Depends on the club? Single guys are
more, couples are less. Single guys are
more, couples are less. I like that you
guys get a discount. Did she get half
off?
I'm so happy I didn't start this [\h__\h]
This is This is good. I'm I'm the victim
right now.
Do you guys have to wear like masks and
stuff or like everyone just goes in as
is?
Oh, that's not as fun. Yeah, everybody
should [\h__\h] dress up.
You do sometimes? What do you go as?
Professor Xavier?
>> [cheering]
>> Still got on my [\h__\h] cowboy hat.
Why, dude?
>> [laughter]
>> You have a cowboy job?
You Oh, you used to ride bulls.
Three championships? Two championships.
You could have lied and [cheering] said
three. We all would have believed you.
If you would have said 15 championships,
we all would have been like, "Yep."
You could have lied to us entirely.
What's up? What's your record time?
Eight Eight six?
Eight [cheering] seconds. Damn, dude,
that's way too long, right, fellas?
What are you showing off for, man?
>> [laughter]
>> You what now? Makes for some of the best
rodeo sex you can have, though.
Am I talking to [\h__\h] bull power right
now?
You are You are the most fitting person
I've ever met to wear a cowboy hat thus
far. Usually
>> [cheering]
>> Usually I just meet people who love
camping with their buddies.
What's the Marine Corps doing over
there, dude? Marine Corps.
>> [cheering]
>> That is awesome, man.
Been around to many places. Been to many
places. I can write a [\h__\h] book about
myself. You can write a book. You should
write a book, dude. Don't do an audio
book, but
not many people speak Copenhagen.
>> [laughter]
>> When he comes, he just goes
How long you guys been married?
About a year. About a year? Oh, okay,
this makes so much more sense. How long
you been together?
Um
We've known each other 20-something
years. Oh, you've known each other for
over 20 years. Oh, okay. And then
you were like
I didn't find anybody.
>> [cheering]
>> You want to
8 seconds.
What happened to your [\h__\h] leg, dude?
>> [laughter]
>> I just noticed you have a you have a you
have a you have a boot on. What
happened?
Fell off a curb. You fell off a curb?
We are seeing the full spectrum of men
here tonight. We are seeing
>> [applause]
[cheering]
>> from
a man who rides dinosaurs
to a man who can't step off a 6-in curb.
Bro, do you have on a cowboy hat?
You waited a second like there was
anybody else who was even possibly
wearing a cowboy hat. What's your name,
man?
Who you here with?
What's your name, wife?
Cassandra. Nice to meet you. Does he
wear this all the time? Yeah, I got used
to it. You got used to it. Isn't that
what marriage is all about?
You meet somebody and you get used to
it.
Do you have a a cowboy job? No,
I'm a firefighter. You're a firefighter?
>> [cheering]
>> When was the last fire that you fought?
Literally yesterday? Man, I would love
to believe you were white before you
went in.
Your name was Tyler.
And it was hot as a [\h__\h] in there and
he came out and he was like, "It's
Tyrone."
That is awesome, man. All firefighters
are so cool. You ever been in a
calendar?
No?
Bro, what's your station called?
Station two? Station two, got to come
out with a calendar, man.
You You got to do February.
It's Black History Month, in case
God, that is embarrassing for y'all, but
And Cassandra, what do you do?
You're a teacher? Man, isn't that crazy
that that's way more dangerous than what
he does?
What do you teach? Like what what grade?
You with infants right now? You a
babysitter.
Our I love cowboys. Huh?
What did you say? I love cowboys.
Why are you singing it?
What's wrong WITH THE COWBOYS?
WHAT IN THE DIXIE Chicks is going on
right now, dude?
You got hair under there?
Yeah? No. No, you bald? Or you hat
fishing?
It does look clean.
Think about it.
>> [laughter]
>> I thought I saw a cowboy hat over there.
It actually there it is. What's up, man?
Why do you know that?
>> [laughter]
>> He walked past you and you smelled him?
That's so creepy.
What if the front row would have done
that when she walked by the [\h__\h] if
everybody was like
>> [laughter]
>> You don't smell people on purpose when
they walk by.
>> [laughter]
>> What's he smell What's he smell like?
Dandelions and Copenhagen?
What cologne do you wear?
Sexy for him?
>> [laughter]
>> You broke your back in two places? Doing
what?
>> [laughter]
>> A parachute accident?
It's the whitest way to get injured,
dude.
Whitest way.
You're making us look terrible right
now. You were You were in the service?
Which branch?
Army? Oh, good [\h__\h] Thanks for your
service.
>> [applause]
>> Was it a equipment malfunction or you
land wrong?
Equipment? That's like the worst That's
like the worst thing that could happen.
I've been I've been skydiving four times
and I'm I'mma keep the dude strapped
[music] to my back.
Cuz I know for the military if you're if
you're any kind of paratrooper, they
make you learn but you The first time
you jump out of plane is by yourself,
right?
See, that's [\h__\h] insane.
Anybody with even slight depression
would be like, "You know what?
>> [laughter]
>> If I just think about it for another 35
seconds, it'll take care of itself."
>> [laughter]
>> I don't trust myself. Do you guys have
that thing where like if you stand next
to like a railing on a balcony like you
feel like your body's going to go [\h__\h]
it.
That's the feeling I would have by the
parachute by myself and I would be like,
let's go. [laughter]
Was it during training or were you
stationed were you getting stationed
somewhere?
We were on a mission in
Iraq. You were on a mission in Iraq. I
don't think you're supposed to talk
about this.
Was this your first mission? No. Oh,
thank god.
Well, imagine your first time you're
like, let's [\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> I know there aren't trees there, but if
I pictured trees.
>> [laughter]
>> Well, first and foremost, thank you for
your service.
Um
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> Se- second, I still want to know what
you smell like.
>> [laughter]
>> Smell like murder.
>> Cuz with a war veteran it will get dark
real quick, man.
Smells like what it looks like to take a
man's life and watch his breath leave
his body.
>> [laughter]
>> Sexy for him.
Man, you got a [\h__\h] cowboy hat in
here. What's up, dude?
What
>> [cheering]
>> is good? Oh, put that back on
immediately. Oh, [\h__\h] I didn't realize.
Oh, I didn't realize I was talking to a
thumb. My bad. It's a good look for you,
bro. I'm so jealous. I could never wear
a cowboy hat, dude. I would I would look
like Heath Ledger butt [\h__\h] me on a
mountain, dude.
Dude, I would I would like I have a
10-gallon [\h__\h] Like I could never
pull off some [\h__\h] like that.
>> have the head for I don't have the head
for it? Oh, all this hair is that was
getting in the way?
>> [laughter]
>> Sorry. Sorry.
Do you Do you Do you have Do you have a
cowboy job?
I do. What do you do?
I am an investor in ranching. You're an
investor in ranching.
Like the dressing?
I'm like farms and [\h__\h]
Farms and [\h__\h] How do you invest in a
ranch? Like you like what what are some
qualifications?
You got to have the intelligence to
invest IN
YOU JUST GOT TO SOUND like that. That's
all you got to do.
So what are you looking to do? I'll tell
you what, it's yours. It's yours. As
much money as you want.
>> [laughter]
>> Accents is so terrifying cuz like it's
so endearing, but like it feels like you
could say the N-word at any moment. I'm
really good, dude.
You're terrifying, [laughter]
bro.
Getting us in trouble. Getting who in
trouble? Us men. Manly men.
First of all, check your tone, Doug
Dimmadome.
>> [laughter]
>> This is right. I'm trying to speak up
for us, all right? I'm trying to help us
out right now. There's nine of us in
here. We need to unite, okay?
You got weed right there?
Can I have it?
We don't smoke in Texas. Are you from
Texas?
Oh, that makes so much more sense, man.
I thought you managed the [\h__\h] Texas
Roadhouse nearby or something like that.
But you personally don't smoke?
No, sir.
Have you ever?
I have. I was drunk. You were drunk when
you did it?
Are you drunk now?
>> [laughter]
>> I'm trying to
Double or nothing.
>> [cheering]
>> You want to hit?
Come on, MAN. COME ON.
I'M going to toss it to you.
>> [laughter]
>> You actually want me TO
SMOKE IT?
WHY YOU TREAT ME LIKE I'M A COP RIGHT
NOW? YOU'RE LIKE, this is drugs I'm
holding right now.
And you want to watch me do it.
>> [cheering]
>> Now, make sure you're hitting the right
end of it. Don't [\h__\h] Don't suck on
the USB port.
Oh, [\h__\h] Oh, [\h__\h] Hey, stop.
[cheering] Stop. Stop. Stop.
Oh, no.
Oh, NO. NO. [cheering]
NO.
I NEED YOU TO SIGN A WAIVER IMMEDIATELY,
DUDE.
We just killed a guy, dude.
That was WAY TOO MUCH.
>> [laughter]
>> I CAN'T SEE IT. OH, THERE WE GO. OKAY.
Thank you.
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> You know you're still standing, right?
We actually didn't get your name. What
was it?
TC.
Okay. You mean like [laughter]
THC?
If your middle name is Henry, I'll lose
it right now.
Are you okay? Careful.
What's your middle name, TC?
Terry Cunningham, TC.
Terry Cunningham. Real quick, what's
your social security number?
Who Who gave this to you?
A stranger.
>> [laughter]
>> Who'd you text? Who do you think some
texts is, man?
Sit down, Statue of Liberty.
I'm 65 640. You're 65?
>> [laughter]
>> We know We We can hear you if you sit
down. You don't have to keep doing
squats, man. Last time somebody was up
here like this talking to me, he was in
prison. And like, "Officer, [laughter]
actually what happened was
the other wife was 35.
I want to
How was that? February the 7th I turned
65 and she's 41. And 41? Where did you
guys meet? A lot of zeros.
A lot of zeros? Did you think he said he
bought her?
>> [laughter]
>> Wow.
Some Texas traditions never die. That's
crazy. He said, "I got a dating app and
it's called Chase Bank, [\h__\h] WHAT YOU
>> [laughter]
>> WHAT, MAN?
I'M GOING TO TELL you I felt
I'm hung like a mule.
He said he's hung like a mule. And you
asked me why
I'm 65
and she's 41. Four questions ago I asked
that.
>> [laughter]
>> Why
do you
deserve
this?
Are you asking me why I think you
deserve her? No.
>> That's a deep question.
Why do you think I deserve a
41-year-old?
>> No, I'm asking how you met. I didn't say
deserve. It wasn't that deep at all.
I guess you don't.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> Oh my god. Man. What's up, man?
Why you standing like you doing magic
right now?
FROM THE WINDOW
>> [laughter]
>> TO THE SWEAT DROP DOWN MY BALLS. ALL
THESE [\h__\h] CRAWL. ALL THESE SNEAKY
[\h__\h]
Look how big this [\h__\h] drink is right
here.
You got That looks like the [\h__\h] you
throw on a head coach after you win the
Super Bowl, bro.
Your Your's is a different thing.
It's a mule? No, that's a mule.
>> [cheering]
>> SIT DOWN, CT.
NO, HE'S GOOD. HE'S GOOD. He's chilling.
He's chilling. He's chilling.
>> [laughter]